(Sheldon:)which can all be harmful
to an unborn baby.
No HoneyBaked Ham
in a hot tub... got it.
(Sheldon:)Oh, no bubble baths either.
(Sheldon:)They can increase the risk
of a urinary tract infection.
(Leonard:)Okay, have fun.
(Sheldon:)Oh, and no swordfish, king
mackerel, shark or tilefish,
(Sheldon:)which are all high in mercury.
(Leonard:)We're leaving now!
(Sheldon:)Oh, and no contact with
guinea pigs
(Sheldon:)or hamsters or their droppings,
(Sheldon:)uh, no-no cat litter boxes,
no paint fumes...
(Penny:)Okay, we're leaving,
love you, bye!
(Sheldon:)Boy, do I love restrictions.
(Penny:)Hey.
(Howard:)Where is everybody?
(Amy:)Oh, we're the first ones here.
(Penny:)Oh.
(Howard:)Cool.
(Sheldon:)Yeah.
(mellow jazz music playing)
(Howard:)You know, I don't
remember the last time
(Howard:)it was just you and me
hanging out.
(Amy:)Oh, I do.
It was three years ago.
(Howard:)Oh, yeah, and we said
we should do it more often.